

Alexandra Kharytonova

Nationality **Ukrainian** Age **24**

Phone / What's Up: +971 54 561 1134 zapozhanova@gmail.com

I'm goal oriented, loyal and committed person with a degree in Journalism and different type of qualifications. I'm seeking for new opportunities in an international company to improve efficiency of the company and myself by implementation of the key qualities gained in:

- Journalism (research adjustment, delicate work with information)
- Design (creativity, supervision on all levels)
- Sports (resourcefulness, ambition, target - driving personality)
- and F&B business (customer orientation, problem solving, social skills).

Work experience

Senior Marketing Executive

(May 2019 - current time)

«Gulf Environment & Waste FZE»

marine waste management company Dubai, UAE

- Managing & Coordinating a team of indoor / outdoor sales & marketing department
- Coordinating working process of operation department

- Writing company guidelines & manuals
- Making market researches & creating strategic plans
- Creating & working with databases
- Preparing documentation and overseeing tender participations & vendor registrations
- Organizing Company's Participation in Oil Spill Exhibition
- Designing digital materials (banners, brochures, presentations)
- Handling print run activities
- Evaluating progress and preparing detailed reports

Receptionist/Guest Relations

(Dec 2017 - May 2019)

«The MAINE Oyster Bar&Grill»

restaurant / bar Dubai, UAE

Managing the front desk

- Accommodating special needs or requests, ensure the group's requirements are met
- Assisting customers with answers to queries, and offering solutions to issues
- Developing strong communication and line reporting procedures
- Coordinating and overseeing the implementation of policies, standards and guidelines

Receptionist / Reservationist

(Dec 2016 - Dec 2017)

«Hakkasan» fine dining restaurant Dubai, UAE

Exude a warm, friendly, and welcoming disposition

to guests as they arrive

- Always be willing to help, assist, and direct guests within the venue
- Monitor the open dining sections of the restaurant
- Send daily /monthly reports regarding future/past/ current reservations
- Office administration

Project Manager

(Jan 2016 - Oct 2016)

LLC «Budinvest» construction firm Kiev, Ukraine

- Planning, executing, monitoring & closing government tender of compound energy-saving renovations
- Negotiating with vendors in order to reach profitable agreements

- Obtaining permits and licenses from government authorities
- Supervising European brunch opening
- Managing HR department (hire/fire/transfer contractors & other staff)
- Compiling and preparing reports, presentations and correspondence
- Managing databases and filing systems
- Managing relationships with key stakeholders

Designer / Retoucher

(Mar 2015 - Jan 2016)

«Color Consulting» publishing house Kiev, Ukraine

- Conceptualizing visuals based on requirements
- Creating images and layouts using design software
- Prepare rough drafts and present ideas
- Develop illustrations, logos and other designs using software or by hand
- Reviewing photos, editing and making necessary
- Liaise with editors, photographers and advertising reps and advise on future projects

EDUCATION

Journalist Sep 2012 - May 2017 Kiev National University of Culture and Arts

Editor-in-chief of the official department journal Class leader

QUALIFICATIONS

Bachelor degree in journalism

Master of Sports in ballroom

Professional print layout designer

Professional retoucher **WSET** Level 1 in wines

ABOUT

Excellent communication

Excellent fast learning skill

Great in time management Perfect user of "MS Office", "Adobe Photoshop", "Adobe InDesign", "Adobe Illustrator" Attentive to details

Strong dependability Significant experience in researches and work with confidential information

A1 in event planning

INTERESTS

Music, art, books, architecture, journalism, marketing, design, travel, selfempowerment.

LANGUAGES

English - fluent Ukrainian - native Russian - native

Thank you for your attention.